You disappeared on me.
We had an appointment.
The mountains called.
Sadie, it's normal
to be affected by what happened.
Death, anyone's, can fill us with urgency.
This is not about what happened.
I didn't really know her, but…
She was the same as me.
Same age, same job.
The one time I was in her house,
it was the same as mine.
Nice, but cold.
Empty, except for one sad houseplant,
which is more than I have.
She died alone.
Sadie, stay present.
No big moves, no big changes.
So don't marry
the rafting guide I just met?
Maybe start with a houseplant.
I'd probably eat it.
My cold, empty house has a cold,
empty fridge.
I'm gonna stop for groceries.
-Let's check in tomorrow.
-Yeah.
No pesticides, more nutrients.
It just tastes better, you know.
Out of 20.
Sorry, guys.
Five, six, seven. Have a good one.
You know you're gonna need
to buy stock in those trackers.
You'd lose your butt
if it wasn't attached to you.
Well, you lost your hair,
and that was attached.
I walked into that one.
Hey, Cole. Are you okay?
Yeah, heard you got dumped.
Tough break, man.
-Edna.
-I gossip when I'm bored.
For your information, it was mutual.
That's what everyone says
after getting dumped.
That's true.
Maybe try being a little less needy,
you know?
Girls don't really like that.
I'm not needy.
We just grew apart.
And I really just don't wanna talk
about it.
You wanna go get high?
I got a edible in the truck.
No, thanks.
Okay. Well, watch my booth.
I'm gonna go get high.
Enjoy.
-Come on. Here.
-Uh, just that one.
-Just this one.
-I'll take one too.
Salmon. Halibut. It's all fresh.
Can I help you?
Yes, thank you. I'm gonna get that one.
Begonia. Nice choice.
-Is that what it is?
-Yeah.
It is pretty.
Yeah.
Don't let any pets eat the leaves.
They can be slightly toxic.
Pretty and slightly toxic.
What is it with me and roommates?
Didn't realize you roomed
with all of my exes.
How much watering does it need?
Every other day or so.
Begonias need a little bit of love.
I'm actually gone a lot for work.
Okay.
Okay, got it. Less love.
What about a snake plant?
They only need watering every two weeks.
Sometimes I'm gone longer,
like a month or two.
Okay.
Sorry, then why do you want a plant
if you're never home?
I'm not never home. I just--
How about if you find me
something a little less needy?
Right. Why not just get a plastic plant?
That's sad.
Well, not as sad as killing a plant.
And some of the new ones,
they look totally real.
No amount of neglect will kill them.
Neglect?
You know what, I'm gonna get this one.
-Yep.
-Thank you.
Sorry, I can't sell you this plant.
I can't sell it to you in good conscience.
Good conscience?
What are you, the patron saint of plants?
I just don't feel comfortable
selling a plant to someone
that can be so indifferent
-towards a living thing.
-Indifferent?
Is this how you speak
to all your customers?
'Cause if you do,
I'm shocked that you sell anything at all.
No, as a matter of fact,
this isn't even my stall.
I just don't wanna be an accomplice…
You're refusing to sell me a plant
that you don't even own?
-That's right.
-Hey, Cole.
-What's going on?
-Hi.
-Are these your plants?
-Yes.
Awesome. 'Cause Farmer Clown here
won't sell me one.
-Farmer Clown. That's funny.
-The plant is $10, honey.
Edna, sh--
All right, you know what?
Hey, want a plant? Here. Cactus.
Requires the bare minimum love
a human can give,
so you'll totally kill it.
You should fire him.
-She's just gonna…
-Have a good one.
RIP, little guy.
-Can you believe that?
-No.
I thought for sure you two
were gonna exchange numbers.
-What?
-Yes.
I thought, under all that stupid fighting,
you were flirting.
-Wait, we were flirting?
-Are you kidding me?
Are you high?
The sexual tension was off the charts.
Edna, watch my stall.
Hey, hey, hey, sorr--
-Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
-Shit.
Hi. Hi. Yep, it's me.
Sorry. Just…
Are you here to rescue the plant?
No. No, I'm not. That's funny.
No, I was just--
Well, I was just wondering
if you wanted to,
you know, go out sometime.
-Are you serious?
-Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I--
I mean, I know we were kind of…
arguing back there,
but I thought that underneath it,
there was…
something.
Something?
Yeah.
I'm wrong, aren't I?
Well, this is embarrassing.
Sorry, sorry. I misread it.
I can use a coffee.
A coffee?
You want to get a-- Yeah. Like, now?
Yes, now.
Get in.
Yeah, well-- Yeah. Yeah.
-I'm Cole, by the way.
-Seat belt.
Yep, yep, yep. Sorry.
I'll just hang on.
Okay.
I like the canal.
It reminds me of Amsterdam.
So, art curators travel a lot?
Oh, yeah. All over the world.
I love it.
Just jumping on a plane, moment's notice,
and then, you know,
stepping out into a new place.
Wow.
Oh, gosh,
don't tell me you're one of those big,
tough guys who's afraid
to leave the country.
Okay, first of all,
thank you for calling me big and tough.
Let's keep that going.
And I travel. I travel a lot.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Yeah, I think the trips
that you plan the least
are the ones that give you the most.
I agree.
Lincoln got shot just across
the street, and he died right next door.
Sounds like you're a big fan of Lincoln.
Well, history in general.
I majored in agriculture,
but I minored in history.
That's my real passion.
You know, I'm writing a book.
-You are?
-Yeah.
History of farming?
No, it's about the rise
and fall of different empires
and the critical role that agriculture--
Yeah, it's about farming.
So how's it going?
Well, it's on pause for now.
My dad got hurt a few years ago,
so I came back to help him with the farm.
So not a lot of time for writing.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. I'll finish it.
You've never seen The Exorcist?
It's a classic.
It's one of the scariest movies ever made,
and they filmed it right here.
I don't know.
I don't get scared by movies.
Yeah,
because you haven't seen The Exorcist.
No, 'cause you can choose
not being scared.
Okay. Little bet. Race me to the top.
And if I beat you,
you gotta tell me what scares you.
-I love this.
-All right. I like the confidence.
Hang on, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me just-- Hang on.
Come on. Put all that in here.
Are you gonna carry all my stuff?
Okay. Wait, wait, wait.
You looking for pity?
That's exactly what I'm looking for.
Oh, my friend.
-You ready?
-Yeah.
And go!
You know, I'm guessing you work out.
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God. I love Monet.
So you can just choose not
to be scared, huh?
When I was six,
my mom and I fled our country…
on a raft.
Oh, my God. That must have been--
Worse than you can imagine.
The sun, the waves,
sharks, people screaming, crying.
I was terrified. Everyone was.
They wanted to go back,
but my mom was so strong.
She kept us all going for five days,
until we made it.
And I still remember how they looked
at her on the beach.
I just, you know, wanted to be like her,
strong and brave.
So that's the day I decided I was never
going to be afraid ever again.
And I'm not.
I believe you.
But it is very cute that you're scared
of this movie with the little girl.
-Oh, my God. This is my own fault.
-That's-- What's the name again?
-It's The Exorcist.
-I have to watch it now.
One of the scariest movies of all time.
You're gonna have nightmares for a month.
-Wow.
-Just watch.
This has just been incredible.
It was great.
And not to be too forward,
but if you ever felt
like getting a drink sometime…
How about now?
Okay.
I know a great place.
Hey!
Thank you.
You are amazing.
How do you make that look cool?
That's rockaoke. No dignity here.
And next up, we have Cole Turner,
turnin' up the heat
-with "20th Century Boy."
-What happened?
-No, no, no, no, no. No, no.
-I might have put your name down.
-Come on, Cole.
-Sadie. Sadie.
Sadie,
I get nervous singing in the shower.
-Just give it a go.
-I'm not a performer.
-Cole! Cole! Cole!
-Cole Turner.
-Where is Cole Turner?
-Please.
I can't.
He's not gonna do it.
Just call someone else.
Give me the mic.
Thank you.
Now, you're out there,
seeing the world, traveling,
meeting interesting people.
It's quite a life.
Lately, I'm not so sure.
Someone I know just died. A coworker.
It got me thinking.
You know, there are all
these things you want in life…
and it's so hard to find someone who--
If only people
could be more like your cactus.
Not needing watering all the time?
Right. Exactly.
-Just living their own lives.
-Yeah.
Not needing someone else,
like, nourishing them.
That makes sense.
Morning.
-What?
-Nothing.
Good night then.
I mean, good morning.
This was quite a date.
You mean a day?
Right. Yeah, that's-- Officially.
That's a first.
Yeah, me too.
Well, goodbye.
Goodbye.
Well, I look forward to our next day.
-Bye.
Be a cactus.
No big moves. No big moves.
Wow.
First farmer?
Yeah.
You know that power you felt?
That's from the land.
Hey, Coleslaw.
Hey, Dad.
Thanks for closing up the stand
for me last night.
Not a problem.
Edna gave me a hand. She was high.
Look who's finally home.
God, take it easy, Mom.
He just got back
from having sex with a stranger,
not fighting the Germans.
Okay, now, come on. Spill the beans.
Well, her name is Sadie, and she is…
She's incredible.
I mean, I know this sounds a little crazy,
but I think she might be the one.
Really? Well, that's fast.
Well, I can't wait to meet her.
Did you tell her you wrestled
in high school?
-No.
-What is this?
You took a selfie
in bed while she was asleep?
Dude, that's weird.
That's what serial killers do
before they kill their victims
and harvest their eyelids.
I was happy.
I wanted to preserve the moment.
-He is doing it again.
-Doing what?
It's just-- Cole, you can get a bit--
Smothering, needy, pathetic,
-desperate, delusional.
-What?
Yeah, stuff like this.
The stupid gifts, the constant texting.
I mean, that's why things never
worked out with Fiona.
Fiona was a bitch.
You're a hopeless romantic,
just like your mom.
Tell her you wrestled in high school.
Look, I'm not needy,
and I'm not smothering.
And for your information,
I've sent Sadie one text today. One.
Three. And some light emoji stuff,
but that doesn't count.
Emoji stuff counts.
He is gonna blow it. Mark my words.
I'm not gonna bl--
She really is great.
You'll see.
Hey. Head in the game, Coleslaw.
Come on. A lot of honey to harvest.
You need some slack?
We're good. Hang on.
Just gotta hook it in. One sec.
Should I get it? I can get it.
It's right here. So easy for me.
Hello?
Good news.
Mortgage refinancing rates
have never been lower.
Any word?
Maybe your phone's broken.
Yeah, maybe you should do a hard reset.
There's nothing wrong with my phone.
No, no, no, I meant with your life.
You know, grow a pair,
move out of your parents' house.
Guesthouse.
Well, I'm sure
there's a logical reason for it.
There is.
He came off way too strong,
so she ghosted him.
Ghosted?
Yeah.
It's when someone breaks off all contact.
For example, let's just say a young lady
makes a horrible,
horrible mistake one night,
and then the guy just keeps
on texting her with emojis,
over and over.
She did not ghost me, okay?
-She did.
-You wanna pick this up?
No.
Hey, pal, you're huffing and puffing.
Why don't you take a hit off your scuba?
Come on, hey. Let's go.
Oh, my God.
Sorry. You did the leave-behind
with your inhaler?
Come on.
Isn't your asthma sad enough already?
It wasn't a leave-behind.
I forgot it in her purse.
And it has one of those tiles on it.
Those tracking things that I use.
All right. Drumroll, please.
The woman of my dreams is in…
-London.
-England?
-London, the Lady in the Mist.
-No one calls it that.
-The Gray Lady.
-No, that's New York Times.
-Are ya sure?
-Yes.
She does travel a lot for work.
Well, there you go. That makes sense.
She probably got called away last minute
on this job and had to rush over there.
You know,
international calling plans and whatnot.
I bet she hasn't even seen your texts.
Yeah, yeah, that makes sense. Okay.
-Exactly.
-Okay, so this is fine?
-Absolutely.
-Yeah.
Cole, you should go over there.
-What?
-Yeah, show up and surprise her.
It'd be a romantic gesture,
something we can tell our grandchildren.
Mom, you can't be serious.
Cole, going to London? No.
Why not? This is a perfect opportunity
to get out there
and grab life by the horns.
She's gonna think you're psycho.
Or she'll think that I'm the kind of guy
that's willing to jump
on a plane at a moment's notice.
Wait, but you're not that kind of guy.
You do not travel anywhere.
-You haven't even left the country.
-That's not true.
He was conceived in Ontario.
Cole, you can do this.
Yeah, but what about the farm?
There's so much to do.
-I can't just leave you here.
-Coleslaw, don't worry about the farm.
-Yeah.
-By the horns. Come on.
Yeah, go to her.
You know what I have?
You remember that spring break
where I was supposed to go to Spain
and I gave up my seat and I got a voucher?
That is my point exactly, Cole.
You missed spring break
to get a stupid voucher,
which you never used.
I mean, that is the type of guy you are.
Not today.
-You still have--
-I've got goose bumps.
Thanks for the warning.
I'm going to London.
So it's not like a weird stalker thing.
It's just a grand romantic gesture.
Yeah, that is amazing, mate.
I mean, I admire your confidence.
5,000 miles to surprise a girl
who you've only met once.
I mean,
that is the epitome of romance, mate.
Yeah, exactly. See, you get it.
Especially if she's the one
who ghosted you.
I was-- Wait, what?
No, no, she didn't ghost me.
She just doesn't
have an international calling plan.
Right.
An international art curator,
doesn't have an overseas calling plan.
That's very unusual.
Talking of romantic gestures,
what's that you got in the back then, hey?
-Is it a little cactus, is it?
-Yeah.
Yeah, this is a little inside joke
between us.
Little cactus.
I'm sure she'll split her sides laughing.
Right, we are nearly here. Tower Bridge.
That'll be 137 quid, please.
-That's kind of a lot, isn't it?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's outrageous.
You never get a cab from the airport
to the center of London.
It'll cost you a small fortune, mate.
Yeah. Toodle-pip.
Take care, now. Thanks very much.
Have a good evening. Have a good night.
Let me tell you how
this will be. One for you, 19 for me.
'Cause I'm the taxman.
Listen to me.
I can't believe I'm quoting
"The Taxman" to you.
So lame. I really am turning into my dad.
It's true what they say.
When you meet a celebrity,
your IQ drops 50 points.
-Where am I?
-It's just-- You're a living legend.
Stopping our shipment in Turkey,
the assassination in Berlin
and now this thing with Elena
and the passcode.
The boss talks about you all the time.
You've become an obsession for him.
"The Taxman killed Elena.
The Taxman has the passcode.
Oh, how I want to find
and murder the Taxman."
And now here you are.
No, no, I'm not a taxman. I'm a farmer.
I came to London to surprise a girl,
and these guys, they jumped me.
Textbook evasion.
Frankly, a little disappointing,
but the performance?
Sublime.
It's like you truly believe
what you're saying.
Because I'm telling the truth.
You have the wrong guy.
My name is Cole Turner.
My passport's right over there in the bag,
in the front flap.
Sublime.
It truly is an honor to torture you today.
Okay, just wait. Wait.
-Normally, I begin with the punching.
-Wait a minute.
You see, it causes me a little pain too.
I'm all about sharing the experience.
My therapist says that I'm an empath,
which means that I'm deeply attuned
to others' feelings.
But alas, the boss is in a real tizzy
about the passcode.
Are you familiar
with the Schmidt sting pain index?
Wait, the what? Wait a minute.
It's a rating system for the pain
caused by the bites and stings of insects.
From the simple ouch
of the western honeybee
to the spray-and-pray
of the Latin American bullet ant
that you can see primed
and ready in that box on the table.
Spray-and-pray is short
for "spray in your pants
and pray for the merciful release
of death."
Excuse me, sir,
will you just grab that bag
for me quickly?
I promise,
this is just a big misunderstanding--
Normally, we like to start slow
and build our way up.
But you are special,
so we begin with the murder hornet.
Shit. Shit.
Unless, of course,
you want to reveal the passcode.
I don't know any passcode!
I'm telling you, you have the wrong guy.
My name is Cole Turner.
Just look at the passport.
It's right there in the bag.
That's just great.
This is going to be fun.
For me, not for you.
Holy shit. Holy shit. Wait, wait--
God. Shit! Shit!
You.
Can you walk?
-What?
-Can you walk, Cole?
Sadie.
Head down, mouth closed.
Follow me before anyone sounds the alarm.
-Know how to use a gun?
-Yeah. Yeah, yeah. But--
Shoot anyone who's not me.
Stay on my six. Let's go.
Sadie. Geez.
Sadie, what the hell is going on?
Who are these people?
Bad guys.
They set a trap for one of our agents,
and you fell into it.
Agents. Art agents?
-Over here.
-Down!
Not an art agent. Got it.
Sorry, there's a lot going on.
Plus those guys drugged me.
Who are you?
CIA. At least,
until they find out about this fiasco.
Keep moving.
My God, you're a spy!
Do you actually know where you're going?
Get down!
Behind you!
You hurt?
No, it's the most amazing thing I've--
I'm so confused.
They kept asking me about the Taxman.
-They asked you about the Taxman?
-No, they think I am a Taxman.
They think you're the Taxman?
That the Taxman would actually fall
for that lazy trap?
They caught the Taxman, and it's you?
-You're the Taxman!
-Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
All right. Check down here.
Freeze!
Shoot him!
-Hey, hey!
-Shoot him!
Just stick 'em up.
You said you could shoot!
At tin cans, not people.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Here.
There! Go!
-Move! Move!
-Where they at?
Art curator, my ass.
I thought you were different too.
Sweet, fun, low-maintenance.
I can't believe I was gonna call you
when I got back.
Cover me.
Cole.
Were you really gonna call me
when you got back?
Yes, until you texted me 11 times
in two days.
-Seven. Emoji stuff doesn't count.
-Yes, it does.
Emoji stuff counts. Move.
-Come on.
-Where the hell are we?
Jump! Cole, come on!
-I swallowed a rock.
-Keep going!
Cover me.
Stop!
Get off the bus.
Come on!
-You're never gonna make it through.
-We're not going that way.
Do you know what you're doing?
Have you done this before?
I'm gonna let you think yes.
I cannot believe you got me kidnapped
and tortured all after one date.
You're the one who flew to London.
Holy shit!
-You are unbelievable!
-What?
You stalkered your way across the ocean
to find me.
That is not cactus behavior!
Don't use stalker as a verb.
And it was a romantic gesture!
I checked your records.
You've never even left the country.
You checked my records?
Who's stalkering now?
Sadie!
Look out!
-Choke him out.
-They usually tap.
He's not going to tap. Just choke him out.
Cole! Are you comfortable?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Is that what I think it is?
It was meant to be a joke.
It was a lot funnier
before I used it to kill a man.
Hey.
Time to walk.
Great khans,
they used to cross these lands.
Brutal killers.
It was said if you wanted to find one,
you had to step over the dead.
The Taxman has a face.
No matches in the intelligence databases.
They must be running him off the books.
Clever.
I've got blood on my hands.
It's the blood of bad men.
We did what we had to.
Is that what you tell yourself?
You're a liar.
I'm not the liar here.
I told you things I've never told anyone.
It was all true.
Not all of it!
Okay, one lie about my job.
I really ate it up too, didn't I?
Especially that sob story
about your coworker that died.
That is low.
That was actually true.
Her name was Elena.
And she really died?
I may have killed her.
What?
She was an enemy agent.
She worked for these guys.
You said she was a coworker.
She was. In a loose sense.
See, this is what I'm talking about.
-It's just lies and lies and more lies.
-It's not lies and more lies.
It's the sub-lie
of the first original lie.
-You're unbelievable.
-Hey.
Fine, I lied about my job.
But you lied about who you are.
Well, excuse me for fudging a few details
to try and impress
the most amazing woman I've ever met.
-Please.
-Who apparently kills coworkers.
Oh, my God!
She killed innocent people, Cole!
Do you know what? I am done with you.
Head down, shut your mouth
and follow my lead.
The sooner I get rid of you,
the sooner I get back to the mission.
Fine. You know what?
I just want to get away from you
and out of here as fast as possible.
You should.
'Cause I've tangled with these guys
before, and they are ruthless.
And now they think you're me,
so they're looking for you, Taxman.
I'll speak with Utami. Buy us some time.
And the passcode?
Looks like Borislov was too slow.
As usual.
But I finally know
what the Taxman looks like,
so I'll find him.
What is this?
He doesn't know anything.
We cannot afford this kind of failure.
The game we play, it's like no other.
If we succeed,
we have wealth, power.
And if we fail, we die.
And that is only if we're lucky.
No, please.
-Please help me.
-No more mistakes.
No.
Get that photo to every bounty hunter
on the continent.
One million dollars. Alive.
He is our only access to that code.
Anyone kills the Taxman,
that bounty moves onto their head.
Be right back.
Just like your farmers' market.
Come on.
Where are you taking me?
Back to your farm,
unless you screw this up.
Stay close.
Be cool.
How you doing?
What? Friendly isn't cool?
Well, well, well, Sadie sunflower.
-Marco.
-Look at you.
Who's your friend?
-I'm--
-He's a civilian I just recovered.
You look ravenous, mate.
Let me put something inside you.
Come on.
Sit down, sit down. Come on, sit down.
The scrap out at the caves.
I should have known that was you.
It was the same people that stole Aztec.
-What's Aztec?
-A biochemical weapon.
Very nasty. Deadly enough
to wipe out the Eastern Seaboard.
That's classified.
They're going to sell it.
Thank you for filling me in.
And they're using those caves
with highly paid protection.
There's only one man
that can pull this off.
Leveque. Disgraced French intelligence.
Played in this sandbox
for most of the war,
and then he went into business
for himself. Arms deals, assassinations.
If he's your target, be careful.
He's a dangerous man.
Anyway, mate, best chaat in town.
Enjoy it.
This is yours, sunflower.
Extra spicy. Just how you like it.
So, are you two, you know, a couple?
-Yeah.
-No.
-Yes. Yeah.
-It was like five months.
-A long time.
You know, we had a lot in common.
You know, work. Not work.
Hey, Mahmoud.
Got it. Subtle.
It's not that.
It's just that sometimes it's easier
to date someone in the same profession.
Always.
Although I wouldn't call
what we did dating.
Please. Can we focus?
Well, that's charming. Very cool.
-Okay.
-Very cool.
I need to find Aztec.
And I need your guys to get Cole
back safely to America.
-Who is he really?
-Nobody.
He's a mistake.
You're the mistake.
She said she was an art curator.
-Wait a second.
-Oh, my God.
You said-- What?
Is he your boyfriend?
He's very funny.
You poor bastard.
You thought you met a hottie, right?
Not a Mata Hari.
But, hey, at least the no pants dance
was worth it.
-Oh, God.
-No, it wasn't.
Come on.
Oh, come on. It was. It was for me.
And I lost a hand.
Lost it.
-Wait. You lo--
-Yeah, gone. It's fake.
-Touch it.
-That's because of Sadie?
-Yeah. You can touch it.
-No. I'm okay. How?
When Sadie and I were together,
we took a little
romantic getaway to Myanmar.
No. It was a mission.
There were many positions.
Don't know if you remember, but anyway.
Things went south.
I got captured, and Sadie took right off.
Turns out that's exactly
what the secret police did to me.
-Oh, my God.
-Yeah, don't worry about it, man.
You got two hands, right,
but only one life.
You know what I miss most, mate? Guess.
-Yeah.
-I used to do that all the time.
Can't do it anymore, can I?
Sorry. You left your boyfriend
to get his hand cut off.
-What the hell is wrong with you?
-Nothing.
I'd have done the same. Mission over man.
Right, sunflower?
Surrounded by lunatics. Wait a minute.
Did you come back to save me or get Aztec?
You were a secondary objective.
-Oh, my God.
-High-priority secondary, I'm sure.
And look at you now, brother. Thriving.
Every word you're saying
is making it worse.
-Every word. I know you're trying. Just--
-Marco.
-This guy.
-Hey.
Are you gonna take him back home or not?
Please say yes.
I'd really hate it if one of my limbs
comes between Sadie and a clean exit.
Sure. Sadie survivors
have to look after each other, right?
Thank you.
Honestly, thank you so much.
You're welcome, babe. Kiss?
No.
Goodbye, Cole.
I'm glad that you survived.
I just wanna be very clear.
Do not ever contact me again.
-Okay?
-With pleasure.
I've already forgotten your name.
Which I'm sure by the way
is fake anyway, so…
-Unbelievable.
-Tell me about it.
She went for a normie,
but that's just lying to herself.
-Yeah.
-Anyway, cheer up, mate.
Stop staring at her. Stop crying.
You're safe now. Come on.
We got a cheeky bottle-o in the back.
On the piss, you and me get drunk,
get smashed.
Alcohol in your mouth.
This is my town. Nothing happens here
that I don't see coming a mile away.
Everything but that I guess.
Walk. Both of you.
-Sorry about Marco.
-Stop talking before you get us killed.
Don't worry. They want him alive.
I don't know what your deal is,
but I'm sure they'll pay for you too.
-They definitely will.
-Cole, shut up. Just--
I'm trying to keep you alive.
Would you rather I say
they wouldn't pay for you?
This is so cute. Get a room.
If it means anything, he's not the Taxman.
Yeah, and I'm not the Grandson of Sam.
Huh? Like the Son of Sam,
the serial killer, but next gen.
I'm the best bounty hunter alive.
Second best.
That was very impressive.
-Shall we?
-Yep, yep. Yep.
You disappointed me, Taxman.
That was too easy.
Now your lady friend's gonna die
'cause of you.
That's funny.
Usually the other way around.
It was you who followed me to Europe.
Lured by your lying.
God, you two need to get a room.
We did. That's what got us into this mess.
Okay, get in the car.
Lady drives. Taxman, you're riding middle.
Scooch, scooch.
Well, Taxman it up.
Don't use Taxman as a verb.
You mind telling us who you are?
They call me the Leopard.
Oh, my God.
Called him the Leopard.
But even leopards get killed by lions,
hyenas, lightning.
Get him out.
And drive.
And who are you?
God. The Bounty Hunter.
Wow. You guys have really good names
in your world.
It's like the WWE, but scarier.
One twist of this ring will send
50,000 volts through your sorry ass.
-Make you wish you were dead.
-Too late.
This is great. Thank you for this.
-Huh?
-No, I was just thinking how happy I am
to have an electrified hockey puck
stuck to my neck with what,
-50,000 volts ready to go into--
-I can't take this.
-Volts into my--
-You really need to shut up.
Wow.
You two should get a room.
You know what? Stop.
Pull over here.
My car is better.
Look, I don't mean to
shake your confidence, God,
but the last two guys didn't make it.
My confidence doesn't shake.
I spent years conditioning myself
to attuning my sense--
Got you, suckers.
If you're collecting the bounty,
where are they taking delivery?
Listen, I'll stash you someplace safe.
If I don't come back for you,
an extraction team will.
So you're really gonna raid a plane
full of armed goons by yourself?
I have to find Aztec. It's my only play.
Wow.
Well, for what it's worth,
I'm sorry about Marco.
God. Seriously?
You know, I'm trying to connect
about a person that just died.
Someone you knew well.
Are you capable of that,
or is that only on first dates?
The rest of the time, it's just
chemical weapons and passcodes
and bullets and death.
Wait, what passcodes?
What do you mean about passcodes?
The bug guy in the cave
kept asking me about passcodes.
Jesus!
-He thinks I have the passcode?
-Yeah.
And you're telling me this now?
I'm sorry.
I was slightly drugged and kidnapped
at the time.
Unbelievable.
Also, in case you forgot, I'm a farmer.
I'm not a super spy.
Why didn't you just ask me
what the torturer was torturing me about?
You are unbelievable!
What? What?
What are the passcodes?
The least you could do is tell me
what I almost died for.
Aztec is inside a high-security case
that cannot be opened without a passcode.
Elena figured out the DNA encryption.
What do you mean, DNA encryption?
The passcode is the entire genetic
sequence of a living organism.
-Insanely long and unique.
-Wow.
I got to Elena
before she could upload it to Leveque.
So they think you have the passcode?
But I don't because she destroyed it.
But if Leveque
is trying to get it from me,
that means he doesn't have it either.
Which means he can't
hand the weapon over to his buyers.
-Which means--
-He still has Aztec.
Which means change of plans.
Do you trust me?
Is that a fucking joke?
Thank you for your honesty.
You're a f-- I cannot believe--
'Cause I'm the taxman
Yeah, I'm the taxman
-Get it?
-The song? Very funny.
You left an impressive trail of blood
bringing us our friend.
-Well done.
-Thanks.
But I don't get paid in compliments.
You'll get your money, bounty hunter.
So you're the Taxman.
CIA's golden boy.
Your pseudonym has generated
as much fun as you have.
But I know you.
I know you because I was you.
Disposable.
Except one day, I found myself
bleeding out in a ditch
on the edge of Kabul.
There was trash everywhere.
And then suddenly, I got clarity.
I had given them everything
and sacrificed everything.
It is a waste of life.
And what are we?
Instruments.
Expendable.
We deserve better.
Tell me the passcode and walk away.
If you don't…
well, we both know how that will go.
I will get what I want…
and you will die anyway.
For nothing.
I swear to God,
I don't know what the passcode is.
I'm not even the Taxman.
Shut up.
Can we get back to business?
Is that my money?
Your payment will be wired soon.
Rumor has it
you stole a weapon you can't use,
so you're overextended.
And now you want me to work on what?
Credit?
No, no.
Cash.
And until I get it,
he doesn't leave my sight.
Or we just kill you.
And make your boss
the guy who offers big paydays
and kills anyone who delivers?
Let me guess.
This is the idiot
who lost him to begin with.
You'll get your cash when you land.
She called you an idiot.
Yeah.
To your face.
Kill her when you touch down.
Get that passcode.
I expect that to be open
next time I see you.
You're not coming?
If anything should go wrong
when you open that case…
…everyone on board dies.
No pressure.
Yes, sir.
We're looking for a genetic sequence.
Do you know what "genetic" means?
That's a cactus.
Thirsty?
-Be smart.
-Sociopath.
I'm not a sociopath.
You know who says that a lot? Sociopaths.
I have dated some crazies in my day,
but you are certifiable.
This is bigger than you and me.
And my plan worked.
Better than I imagined.
Really?
Did you imagine
I'd make it out of this alive?
We found Aztec.
As soon as we land,
we'll take these guys down.
We'll be safe.
The world will be safe. Everybody wins.
What's all this?
What's…
all this?
I would expect more discretion
from the Taxman.
So would I.
So what are you really?
Hired help?
Or just the girlfriend?
Believe me, she's not girlfriend material.
You know, I don't care.
You die either way.
Hey, hey, hey. Wait, wait. Wait.
Who's the idiot now?
I have the passcode.
Bullshit.
He doesn't have it.
I do.
Really?
So we can kill him.
Hey! Wait. Okay. Wait.
The passcode. Now!
Sure. It's in my pocket.
We're good.
Really?
Open it.
Shit!
I can't believe you took a picture of me
while I was sleeping!
Not of you, of us!
I knew you were a creep!
I'm not a creep!
You know who says that a lot? Creeps!
Let me see. Let me see. Let me see.
Oh, my God.
Take the case and go.
-There is a parachute.
-What about you?
Mission over man.
No. No. I gotta stop this bleeding first.
You're losing a lot of blood.
-Just go, Cole.
-I gotta find…
-Cole, go! Go!
-Sadie, I'm telling you right--
Get out of here.
Hey!
Get out of the way, you idiot.
What are you doing?
I have no idea.
Sadie?
God.
I told you to go.
I did.
I just took you with me.
How long was I out?
A while.
Looks like you got creative
with the parachute.
I had a lot of nervous energy.
You got it.
Yeah. Yeah.
-You got Aztec.
-Yeah.
-Wait. Take it easy.
-I mean, do you have a--
You lost a lot of blood.
It was really gross.
I'm sorry. I don't know what to say.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Pardon me. Excuse me. Pardon.
Hello?
Leveque, things didn't go as planned.
The girl sprung the Taxman.
How many times can you lose one man?
Listen carefully.
If we do not deliver
an operational weapon in 48 hours,
our buyers will kill us all.
Now, you find the Taxman,
or they will not have the chance
because I will kill you myself.
Boss. We have a sighting of the parachute.
Good.
You know,
I think, depending on your strength,
we should consider maybe hiking
out of here tomorrow.
Depending on your strength.
You have to tell me. What is this gunk?
It's periwinkle and gavilana.
I found it up the beach,
smashed it up and put it in there
to stop the bleeding
and fight the infection.
-How did you know how to do that?
-I read about it.
Throughout history, every culture has
their own knowledge of the crops they grow
for food or clothing, medicine.
I just don't get why you never left
the country.
-Here we go.
-What? I'm serious.
You're clearly interested in the world.
I wanted to travel. I really did.
I thought I was gonna after I graduated.
You know, research the book.
Then my dad got hurt…
just went home.
He never recovered?
No, he did. He's good now.
But you know, he's getting old.
And you know,
we got to keep production high to compete,
and business is changing.
Anyway…
They need me there.
Do they?
What about you? Your mom must be proud.
Daughter's a CIA agent. Right?
I'd like to think she'd be.
My mom died when I was very young.
-God, I'm sorry. I didn't know.
-It's okay.
I promise. It happened so long ago.
You know, and then after she died,
I found the army.
You know,
somewhere where I could put my focus.
And then the agency, they gave me purpose.
Our struggles make us stronger. Right?
Any other family?
In my line of work,
it's better being alone.
Is it?
For what it's worth, I think
that any parent would be very proud…
of you.
You know what?
I just can't believe that that little shit
is still in one piece.
Maybe you can keep
a cactus alive after all.
Maybe.
I'm sorry about the selfie.
I'm sorry about the gag.
Call it even?
Deal.
Run!
Get me the Taxman alive, kill the girl,
and I'll get Aztec.
Move! Move!
There she is.
Attention.
This is the United States Marines.
Safety your weapons
and drop them on the ground.
Damn it.
Where's the case?
Agent Rhodes. It's time to go home.
We're fine. Thanks.
Let's go.
-That's not too tight on you now, is it?
-No.
Okay. Just wanna make sure.
Yeah, that's good.
A polygraph, Jackson?
Are you really
this desperate to jump ahead of me?
I'm just doing my job, Rhodes.
No, if you were doing your job,
you'd be out there looking for Aztec.
If you had done yours,
we never would have lost it.
Well, it wasn't her fault.
She was just trying to save me.
Of course.
The boyfriend,
accidentally along for the ride.
Didn't it ever occur to you
that he could be a foreign asset,
trying to compromise your mission?
Yeah. Six-foot honeypot sent to kiss
and nibble the secrets right out of you.
Patti, just watch the machine, please.
Right. Sorry.
We both know you checked him out.
He's a civilian, and he's clean.
Some civilian.
Because you chose his life over thousands,
if Aztec is ever deployed.
I let my emotions cloud my judgment.
Wait a minute.
Are you saying you think
it was a mistake to save my life?
Yes.
That's great.
Cole, I'm sorry, but they're right.
One life compared to thousands.
Yeah, no, I get it.
Mission over man justifies everything.
Marco's hand,
using me as bait at the airstrip.
-I get it.
-You used him as bait?
-Yes.
-No.
Well…
Marco was right about you.
You should date someone just like him.
Completely cut off
from emotional connection
-and not afraid to lose a limb.
-What?
You know what?
Marco was right, but not about that.
We only have one life,
and you are too afraid to live it.
Says the one-handed dead guy.
What's happening?
Cole, you went to your parents' house
to help them.
But I don't think they need you anymore.
I think
they're just an excuse to avoid life.
Look who's talking.
Your job, the duty, the sacrifice,
that's your excuse to keep people out.
I think you're afraid
to get close to people.
'Cause if you do, you might lose them.
-Just like you lost your mother.
-Hey!
You don't talk about her!
And I'm not afraid of anything.
You two need to get a room.
-Oh, my God.
-Patti,
he's not even hooked up to the machine.
I'm sorry. But, you guys,
the sexual tension in the room is just--
The boss wants to see you.
So much for starting with a houseplant.
I know she pulled you into this…
but…
you're still in deep shit.
You're facing prosecution.
For what? Visiting a girl in London?
Why are you protecting her?
I know this looks bad. I can fix it.
We can still get Leveque.
You were always my favorite, Sadie.
But you going rogue,
there's nothing I can do.
What do you mean?
She didn't lose Aztec, did she?
No, no, no, no, no.
She's working an angle.
-No. No.
-Looking to cash in.
Sadie would never do that.
You let Aztec
get into the hands of a known threat.
You're suspended,
pending a full investigation,
but you know how these things go.
You'll be lucky to have a job
at all when it's done.
Look at what she does.
And this is just the last six months.
She's a liar and a killer, Cole.
Is that someone you want to protect?
Take home to Mom?
Oh, my God.
What am I looking at? A houseplant?
Well, it's not a houseplant.
That's an amaranth. A crop.
Farmed in the Americas
for thousands of years, mostly for food,
but often used in rituals by the Aztecs.
Oh, my God. The plant wasn't hers.
She took it from Horvath, the scientist.
He was obsessed with the Aztecs' use
of human sacrifice.
The genetic sequence
of that amaranth is the passcode.
I'll be damned.
I want that plant retrieved
from Elena's apartment now.
You know, we can use this to lure
in Leveque. We get a message to him.
"The Taxman is ready
to sell the passcode."
He'll never go for it.
Unless we bait the hook.
The passcode is divided
into four segments.
Send Leveque the first.
What? Give him part of the key?
That's insane.
Exactly. The agency would never allow it.
So if the Taxman is doing it, that means
he went rogue and the offer is real.
Leveque is desperate. He'll bite.
That means we're gonna need the Taxman.
Me? No, no, no way.
It's only for appearances.
He won't even get near you.
Well, then what do you need me for?
Use a dummy. Put Jackson in a disguise.
That's a great idea.
Mr. Turner, I know you don't want
to do this, but I also know that you will.
As long as Leveque thinks
you're the Taxman, you're in danger.
Well, then put me in protective custody.
Hide me just until you find the guy.
What about your family?
-What about my family?
-Guys like Leveque, they never stop.
The only way
to guarantee your family's safety
is to take him off the board.
No, no, no.
Hey, Cole. Cole, it's too dangerous.
They're using you.
Well, that's funny because he just said
the same thing about you.
Remind me, which one of you
can't stop risking my life?
I know you're angry,
but this is a mistake.
Protecting the people you love
is never a mistake.
Maybe one day you'll care enough
about someone to understand that.
Rhodes.
Come on, you have to let me run this.
I know more about Leveque's operation
than anyone.
Go home, Sadie. And stay there.
What do you think?
What do I think? I think it is a trap.
Test it.
It's genuine.
Maybe it's not a trap.
Or maybe it is just a very good one.
Either way, what choice do we have?
Boss.
Mr. Utami. Pleasure to see you again.
Funny. When you accepted my first payment,
you neglected to mention
that you didn't have the passcode.
We will have it soon.
Aztec will be yours as promised.
Mine, I believe.
You're meeting the Taxman?
We'll go together.
If he has the passcode, we conclude
our business. If he doesn't, I kill you.
Mr. Utami, one condition.
Whatever happens, the Taxman dies.
So be it.
Turner,
get in there and make it look good.
You'll be in and out in 20 minutes.
Stop messing with your collar. Sounds
like a goddamn thunderstorm in here.
Sorry, I hate suits.
-How many guys do you have?
-Including me? Three.
Three? What do you mean? Three guys total?
You have three guys total?
You can't do this with three guys.
The CIA can't operate on US soil.
We had to travel light.
Travel light?
What are you, backpacking through Europe?
You're the CIA. What does that even mean?
Travel light?
Calm down. Leveque's men
just need to see you in there.
We'll arrest him as soon as he shows.
You got to play the part.
You're not a farmer anymore. Remember?
You're the Taxman. Now, get in there.
Hi, welcome in.
Table for Mr. Taxman.
Yes, right this way.
Cheers!
Everything will be fine.
We've got it all under control,
and the bad guys will never get near you.
Three guys.
They're here.
We got eyes on the target.
He has the weapon.
Let's get ready to move.
Jackson. What was that?
-Cole.
-What?
Get out of there.
Go now? Okay. Okay. Okay.
Does this mean we lose Leveque?
Jackson, what happens to my family
if you lose Leveque?
I'm staying.
She's coming.
I know it.
Well, well, well, what a romantic spot
for our first official date.
I brought a little something special
for us to open up.
And some chaperone. Hope you don't mind.
I apologize. Yours are no longer with us.
It is more intimate this way, no?
Are you all right, Taxman?
I hate to think something
might ruin our night.
-Thank you.
-For what?
For helping me with my chaperones.
Saves me the hassle
of having to kill them myself.
It was my pleasure.
But somehow I don't believe you.
Well, I don't care what you believe.
My intention is to walk out of here
a very rich man and disappear.
The great Taxman betraying his country.
No. Why would you do that?
What you said to me
about wasting my life. Made me think.
Let's not delay this new beginning.
The passcode.
Money first.
And… my price doubled.
Negotiations are over.
Well, negotiations are never over anytime.
You know, it…
actually reminds me of this one time
I was…
I was selling missiles to a arms dealer,
and he was haggling and haggling,
wouldn't stop.
Finally, he bought the missiles and…
And he comes back an hour later,
and he says,
"I paid too much for these missiles.
I want a better price," you know.
And I said, "That's not how this works.
You can't haggle now."
He says, "I want a full refund.
I don't even want the missiles anymore."
I said to him, "Look,
I can't take these missiles back.
-You've had them for an hour."
-Enough!
The passcode now!
Or you both die.
He gets very upset.
Do you have the passcode?
Do you have the passcode or not?
'Cause it is going to be very painful
for both of us if you do not.
My friend?
I'm sorry I'm late.
Glad you could make it.
Well, what can I say?
You might be growing on me.
What is this?
An opportunity for me to check out
all the players.
Mr. Utami, since you're the one
with the money, I'll address you.
The price of the passcode
is exactly half of Leveque's fee.
Wire it to this account
after that case opens.
You are the Taxman.
Here to collect.
In that case, then who are you?
My boyfriend.
Damn straight.
If you have the passcode,
I accept your terms.
-Mr. Utami--
-Open it.
You have the passcode?
I still have friends at the agency.
Wait a minute. You can't open that.
When the people you love are in danger,
you do whatever it takes.
Voilà.
Aztec, as promised.
Thank you very much.
It's a pleasure doing business with you.
Yes, thank you very much.
However, my business is not yet finished,
but you are.
What makes you think I will let you two
out of here alive?
The ten-million-dollar bounty
I put on your head might help.
I don't know
how many bounty hunters are here,
but they definitely know about you.
Know what's funny?
Like you, I didn't actually have
the money until just now,
but the bounty hunters
didn't need to know that.
They just needed to know where you were.
Okay, Leveque.
You're worth a lot of money.
-I'll take that from you.
-Gun!
Nobody move!
You are so dead, my friend.
Tell your guys not to do anything stupid.
And what is the plan, huh?
Now what are you going to do?
Do nothing. You're coming with me.
How can I do nothing and come with you?
You idiot,
how are you going to get out of here?
I'll give you 20 million to shoot
this one. To kill her right now.
Are you ready?
Ready for what?
No, I'm not. I'm definitely not. What--
You flush them forward.
I will cut around. Get the vial. Now! Go!
Stairs.
Where you going?
Sadie?
I'm an ally.
-Jonas?
-I have missed you so much.
Listen, it was never gonna
work out between us.
No, no, no, no. Of course it wasn't.
I was losing too many body parts.
That's not sustainable.
But if you look on the bright side,
I still have 20 vision.
Jonas,
I'm in the middle of something here.
I know. Look, losing the eye sucked.
But I'll tell you,
getting this thing blown off,
that was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
Seriously, it changed my whole life.
I'm a good, solid, active listener now.
That's the other ear.
I didn't need the ear.
You keep going. You do what you do.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
All right, yes.
That looked cool, but cheating.
You're not the Taxman.
Who the hell are you?
What she said.
I'm the boyfriend.
No!
You need to get me out.
No, you stay here.
Give me the weapon.
Damn it.
Come on, Taxman. Give me my weapon.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Squandering all this talent.
-You and I could've had so much working--
-There's nothing you have that I want.
What is it that you want, huh?
You want a boyfriend? So pedestrian.
He does not know you.
He does not see the real you.
Cole?
Cole!
Get me over there!
You look amazing in that dress.
And you should wear more suits.
-He almost died in a refrigerator.
-But I did not do that. That was his.
-In a refrigerator, for how long?
-Was it you?
-Why would I put a cat in a fridge?
-What are you talking about?
-You didn't put him in.
-I think it's pretty clear.
-You didn't notice him when you closed it.
-Not the cat story.
-He did it.
-Yeah, the cat story again.
So, Europe by rail.
That sounds so romantic.
You want to write a book,
you got to do research.
What's Sadie supposed to do
in all these places
while you're reading musty old scrolls
about farming?
Don't worry about me. I have a whole list
of clients I need to hunt down.
I'm sure you're gonna get them all, dear.
I know I will.
Yeah, she will.
Art curating is so much more exciting
than I imagined.
-Yeah
-Yeah. God, like, I want to be you.
I mean, except the part where
you're sleeping with my brother.
What?
Just, please.
-So…
-We're at the dinner table.
You guys promise to take care
of this little guy while we're gone?
Yes, I love succulents.
-How hard is it to keep a cactus alive?
-Sometimes harder than you think.
-But worth it.
-Very much.
I mean, we're talking about a cactus.
Right?
You water it once a month.
-Or are we talking-- Okay. It's subtext.
-Okay.
-That's right.
-There's a--
-There's a hidden meaning.
-Yep. There's-- And then--
-Levels.
-Okay, that's great.
-Your mother and I have a--
-There's no "mother and I" story.
-It's not about a cactus.
-No, it is not.
It involves wrestling.
Did he ever tell you that he wrestled
in high school?
Keep drinking your wine.
Okay.
-Hey, babe, I'm sorry I'm late.
-Nice car.
Are you sure the CIA didn't let you
keep Utami's money after all?
You wish. I'm borrowing this.
How was your meeting
with Professor Kirkland?
-Really good.
-Yeah?
He gave me some amazing research.
This is Raul.
He's an arms dealer,
but business stays in the car.
Date night.
Us time.