[door beeps]
[woman] Thanks.
[indistinct chatter]
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
[doorknob rattling]
- No.
- [bangs door]
[sighs]
- [gun cocking]
- Hands up. Hands up!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Forgot all the cameras, bub?
Look, Dr. Brenner asked for
me specifically. Okay?
How else do you think I got in here?
[Hopper scoffs]
What's your name again?
It's Jim Hopper.
Chief Jim Hopper.
Yeah, I've got Jim Hopper... [grunts]
- [man on radio] Come again?
- [grunts]
[both panting]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Hey...
you mind if I borrow this one?
- [beeps]
- [door buzzing]
[door locks]
- [liquid pouring]
- [Lonnie] Drink.
It'll calm your nerves.
Help you think straight, yeah?
I don't know what to do.
I know. I know.
[sniffs] This whole time...
I... I could... I could feel him.
He was...
He was so close. He
was... he was right there.
- I knew he was alive.
- [thunder rumbles]
Our hands... our
hands were almost touching.
Now it's like I... uh...
[sobbing] God, it's like
I can't feel him anymore.
- Don't look at me like that.
- Like what?
Like how everybody is looking at me.
- Like I'm out of my damn mind.
- Hey.
You're not gonna like this,
but I think you need to seriously consider
the possibility that all this...
It's in your head.
[scoffs]
- You remember your Aunt Darlene?
- No.
No, this is not that.
I mean, when something
like this happens,
your mind makes up stuff
for you to cope, you know?
I mean, Jesus, there's a
funeral tomorrow for our little boy
and you're saying his body is fake.
He's in the wall.
I mean, how do you explain that?
- [stammers]
- It just doesn't make sense. It doesn't.
- At least go talk to a shrink or...
- [sighs]
- What about Pastor Charles or someone...
- I don't... Well, they can't help.
Joyce, you just told me...
that Will is gone.
- What else is there to do?
- [sniffles]
Hey.
[sniffles]
[Hopper] Will?
Will?
[Mike] What was Will saying?
Like home... Like home...
but dark?
[Lucas] And empty.
[sighs] Empty and
cold. Wait, did he say cold?
I don't know. The stupid radio
kept going in and out.
[sighs] It's like riddles in the dark.
Like home. Like his house?
Or maybe like Hawkins.
Upside down.
- What'd she say?
- Upside down.
- [Lucas] What?
When El showed us where Will was, she
flipped the board over, remember?
Upside down.
Dark. Empty.
Do you understand what
he's talking about?
- No.
- [Mike] Guys, come on, think about it.
When El took us to find Will, she
took us to his house, right?
Yeah. And he wasn't there.
But what if he was there?
What if we just couldn't see him?
What if he was on the other side?
What if this is Hawkins and...
this is where Will is?
The Upside Down.
Like the Vale of Shadows.
[Hopper] Will?
- Will?
- [alarm blaring faintly]
Will?
[alarm continues]
- [pressing button]
- [indistinct chatter]
[guards yelling]
I see him! Hey! Stop!
[Dustin] "The Vale of Shadows
is a dimension that is a dark
reflection or echo of our world.
It is a place of decay and death."
[Hopper] Will?
"A plane out of
phase. A place of monsters.
It is right next to you, and
you don't even see it."
- [electricity crackling]
- [Hopper coughing] Will?
Will?
An alternate dimension.
But... how... how do we get there?
You cast Shadow Walk.
In real life, dummy.
We can't shadow walk, but...
maybe she can.
Do you know how we get
there? To the Upside Down?
[sighing] Oh, my God!
[coughing]
[exclaims softly]
What the hell?
[rhythmic pulsing]
[gasps]
[Hopper] Hey!
Hey! Hey!
[theme music playing]
_
Hey, kid.
What's going on?
Your dad's, uh, gonna stay here
tonight. [stammers] On the couch.
[Lonnie] Yeah, I'm here as
long as you need me, okay?
How are you holding up?
What happened?
- Don't worry about that.
- Mom...
that thing you saw
before, did it come back?
Jonathan, that's enough.
[sighs]
Can we talk?
Alone?
- You need to leave.
- Look, I know you're upset.
We all are.
But you need to listen to me. Your
mother is sick. Really sick.
Yeah. Well, you being here,
you're just making
things worse, like always.
- Worse?
- Yeah!
She took down that wall with an ax.
She said that Will was
inside and that he's talking to her.
Yeah. Maybe he was.
This isn't some kind of joke.
Your mom was half frozen
to death when I got here.
Trembling, scared out of her mind.
You come in here and you start
feeding into her hallucinations
or whatever the hell
you want to call it,
you're gonna push her
right over the edge.
You hear me?
[sighs] Look, I'm on your side.
I'm here to help.
I'm gonna make things
better around here for all of us.
[scoffs] Thank God you're here.
Do me a favor. At the
funeral tomorrow, just behave.
If not for me, for your mother.
Take that down. It's inappropriate.
- Good.
- Ah! Dad, you're... you're choking me.
Ah... there. It's supposed
to be a little tight.
Looks good.
- [zipper closing]
- Here we go. [sighs]
You look nice, sweetie.
Anything else?
You can borrow my
black heels if you want.
The ones you wore to Cathy's birthday.
I'm fine. Thanks.
[whimpering]
Ugh.
Come on. Time to go.
[groans softly]
- Come on.
- [sighs]
[Pastor Charles] "Fear
not, for I am with you.
Be not dismayed, for I am your God.
I will strengthen you.
Yes, I will help you.
I will uphold you with
my righteous right hand."
It's times like these that
our faith is challenged.
How, if He is truly benevolent...
could God take from us someone
so young, so innocent?
It would be easy to
turn away from God...
but we must remember that nothing,
not even tragedy, can
separate us from His love.
We are here today to find
comfort in the truth of scripture,
- and to surround Will and his family...
- [sniffles]
Just wait till we
tell Will that Jennifer
Hayes was crying at his funeral.
[shushes]
- [Karen] I'm so, so sorry.
- Oh, thank you so much for coming.
Yeah, if there's anything we can do...
I appreciate it. Thank you so much.
Take care, all right? Thanks.
Thanks for coming out.
I see Will the Wise is back.
What's that shooting out of his cane?
Fireballs.
I couldn't find the red
crayon, so that's why it's green.
Oh, well...
if he's so wise, why
does he need fireballs?
Why can't he just, you
know, outsmart the bad guys?
Most of the time, yeah, totally.
But... sometimes the
bad guys are smart, too.
You know?
Yeah.
So he needs the fireballs?
Well, yeah, to burn them to a crisp.
All right. Well, I don't
know who's been raising you,
but I'm gonna get you some new crayons
because it looks like
he's shooting cabbages.
[both chuckle]
[gasping]
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
[dishes clattering]
[exclaims]
[Lucas] Will! Will,
it's us! Are you there?
[Dustin] Can you hear us? We're here!
[Will distorted] Hello? Mom?
- [Lucas] Why can't he hear us?
- [Mike] I don't know!
[Will distorted] Mom, it's coming!
She was there.
[church bell tolling]
This is where we know for
sure it's been, right?
- So, that's...
- Steve's house.
And that's the woods where
they found Will's bike and...
that's my house.
- It's all so close.
- Yeah. Exactly.
I mean, it's all within
a mile or something.
Whatever this thing is,
it's... it's not traveling far.
You want to go out there.
We might not find anything.
I found something.
And if we do see it...
then what?
[sighs]
We kill it.
- What are you doing?
- Just give me a second.
Are you serious?
What? You want to find this thing
and take another photo? Yell at it?
This is a terrible idea.
Yeah, well, it's the best we've got.
What? You can tell someone, but
they're not gonna believe you.
You know that.
Your mom would.
- She's been through enough.
- She deserves to know.
Yeah, and I'll tell her...
when this thing is dead.
I don't know what in
the world caused it.
- Let's take a look, huh?
- Yeah.
Mr. Clarke says he's never
seen anything like it.
Mr. Clarke?
Yeah, he runs the AV Club.
[repairman] That right?
Apparently, some of the less athletic
types go nuts for this stuff.
[engine starting]
[indistinct chatter]
[Mike] Mr. Clarke?
Oh, hey, there.
How are you boys holding up?
[munching]
We're... in... mourning.
Man, these aren't real Nilla Wafers.
[Mike] We were
wondering if you had time to talk?
- We have some questions.
- A lot of questions.
So, you know how in Cosmos, Carl Sagan
talks about other dimensions?
Like, beyond our world?
Yeah, sure. Theoretically.
Right, theoretically.
So, theoretically, how
do we travel there?
You guys have been thinking about
Hugh Everett's Many-Worlds
Interpretation, haven't you?
Well, basically, there
are parallel universes.
Just like our world,
but just infinite variations of it.
Which means there's a world out there
where none of this tragic
stuff ever happened.
Yeah, that's not what
we're talking about.
- Oh.
- We were thinking of more
of an evil dimension, like
the Vale of Shadows.
You know the Vale of Shadows?
An echo of the Material Plane,
where necrotic and shadow magic...
[Mike] Yeah, exactly.
If that did exist, a place
like the Vale of Shadows,
how would we travel there?
- Theoretically.
- [Mr. Clarke] Well...
Picture... an acrobat...
standing on a tightrope.
Now, the tightrope is our dimension.
And our dimension has rules.
You can move forwards, or backwards.
But, what if...
right next to our
acrobat, there is a flea?
Now, the flea can also travel back
and forth, just like the acrobat.
- Right?
- Right.
Here's where things get
really interesting.
The flea can also travel this way...
along the side of the rope.
He can even go...
underneath the rope.
- [boys] Upside down.
- Exactly.
But we're not the
flea, we're the acrobat.
In this metaphor,
yes, we're the acrobat.
So we can't go upside down?
No.
Well, is there any way for the
acrobat to get to the Upside Down?
Well... you'd have to
create a massive amount of energy.
More than humans are
currently capable of creating, mind you,
to open up some kind of
tear in time and space,
and then...
you create a doorway.
- Like a gate?
- Sure. Like a gate.
- But again, this is all...
- Theoretical.
But... but what if this
gate already existed?
Well, if it did, I... I think we'd know.
It would disrupt gravity,
the magnetic field, our environment.
Heck, it might even swallow us up whole.
Science is neat.
But I'm afraid it's not very forgiving.
Whoa.
Hey, Chief!
- [knocking] Hello? Whoa!
- Hey!
- [Powell] Jesus, Chief. You all right?
- What are you doing here?
- We tried calling, but...
- Yeah, the phone's dead.
Hey, so Bev Mooney came
in this morning all upset.
Said that Dale and
Henry went hunting yesterday...
and they didn't come back home.
She thought they were on another
binger, but she's not so sure now.
I think this whole Will Byers
thing has everybody on edge.
- Where was this?
- It was at the station.
No, no. Where did
Henry and Dale go hunting?
Oh. Uh, out near Kerley.
Mirkwood.
What?
Okay.
You go back to the station. I'll
take care of this, all right?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, leave it.
- Oh, hey. Uh, they found Barbara's car.
- What?
Barbara Holland's car. Seems
she ran away after all.
Staties found it late last
night at a bus station.
Funny, right? They keep
doing our job for us.
Yeah. [chuckles] It's funny.
[door closes]
- Is he off his meds again?
- [engine starts]
He's been spending too
much time with Joyce Byers.
That's what I think.
[sighs] What are you doing?
What does it look like I'm doing?
You want to freeze to death all winter?
[hammering continues]
- I told you not to take these down.
- They were in the way, babe.
How long are you gonna
keep those up? I mean, really?
You know, it's a shame what
they've done to this family.
- What?
- The Sattler Company.
I went to the quarry
on the way over here.
I just wanted to look around, you know?
Couldn't believe it. I
just couldn't believe it.
No warning signs, no fence, no nothing.
Ought to be held
accountable if you ask me.
It would take a lot of
energy to build a gate like this.
But that's got to be what happened.
- Otherwise, how'd Will get there, right?
- Right.
What we want to know is, do
you know where the gate is?
Then how do you know
about the Upside Down?
[Mike] Dustin, what
are you doing? Dustin?
- Dustin!
- I... I need to see your compasses.
- What?
Your compasses. All of
your compasses, right now!
What's exciting about this?
- Well, they're all facing north, right?
- Yeah, so?
- Well, that's not true north.
- What do you mean?
I mean exactly what I just
said. That's not true north.
Are you both seriously this dense?
The sun rises in the east, and
it sets in the west. Right?
Which means that's true north.
So what you're saying is
the compasses are broken.
[sighs] Do you even
understand how a compass works?
- Do you see a battery pack on this?
- No.
No, you don't. Because
it doesn't need one.
The needle's naturally drawn to
the Earth's magnetic North Pole.
So what's wrong with them?
Well, that's what I couldn't
figure out, but then I remembered.
You can change the
direction of a compass with a magnet.
If there's the presence of a
more powerful magnetic field,
the needle deflects to that power.
And then I
remembered what Mr. Clarke said.
The gate would have so much power...
It could disrupt the
electromagnetic field.
Exactly.
Meaning, if we
follow the compasses' north...
They should lead us to the gate.
[sighs]
Whoa, whoa, hey, whoa, whoa.
- [exhales] What are you doing here?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- I hope that's not meant for me.
What? No.
Oh, no, I was just...
- thinking about joining softball.
- Oh.
Well, uh...
listen, I'm really sorry.
I mean, even before you threatened
me with the baseball bat.
Okay.
I panicked and...
[sighs]
- I mean, I was a total dick.
- Yeah, you were.
[sighs]
Did you get in trouble
with your parents?
Totally, but...
you know, who cares? Screw 'em.
Any news about Barbara?
- Parents heard from her? Or...
- No.
Hey, listen.
Why don't we, uh, why don't we
catch a movie tonight, you know?
Just kinda pretend
everything's normal for a few hours.
All The Right Moves is still playing.
You know, with your lover boy
from Risky Business? [chuckles]
Yeah, I know.
You know, Carol thinks I
actually kinda look like him.
What do you think? Huh?
♪ Just take those old records ♪
♪ Off the shelf ♪
♪ I'll sit and listen
to them by myself ♪
I just, I... I don't think I can.
I've been really busy with
this whole funeral thing and...
[inhales] with my brother.
It's been really hard on him.
Yeah, sure. Sure, yeah, yeah.
So...
I should go.
Sorry.
I'll call you later. Is that okay?
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
♪ Just take those old records ♪
♪ Off the shelf ♪
♪ I'll sit and listen to them... ♪
[sighs]
- [Joyce] You were here for the money!
- [Lonnie] No!
The money! Admit it!
You aren't here 'cause of Will. You
never cared about him. You never did!
Jesus, Joyce, it was his funeral
today. Do we have to do this right now?
- I can't believe I fell for this.
- I'm here to help, Joyce.
- To help?
- We could use that money for good.
[stammering] Oh, like
maybe to pay off your debts?
To pay for Jonathan to go to school!
- Oh, don't do that.
- Do what?
- Lie to me!
- I'm not lying to you!
Yeah, well, where does he wanna go?
- Huh?
- What?
Where does Jonathan want
to go to college?
We get that money, anywhere
he damn well pleases!
NYU, Lonnie!
He's wanted to go to NYU since
he was six years old!
So then he goes to NYU!
Get out.
Get out!
You need me here, Joyce.
[laughs] Oh, brother, I have
not needed you for a long time!
Oh, no? Look what happened.
[scoffs]
Oh, don't you dare.
- At least I was here!
- Oh, come on, Joyce.
Just look around at this place.
All your Christmas lights.
What the hell am I supposed to think?
You're such a great mom? You're a mess!
Maybe I am a mess. Maybe I'm
crazy. Maybe I'm out of my mind!
But, God help me, I will keep these
lights up until the day I die
if I think there's a chance
that Will's still out there!
Now, get out!
Get out of my house!
[sighs]
[Nancy] You're
supposed to hit the cans, right?
No, actually, you see the
spaces in between the cans?
I'm aiming for those.
Ah.
You ever shot a gun before?
- [scoffs] Have you met my parents?
- [chuckles softly]
Yeah, I haven't shot
one since I was ten.
My dad took me hunting on my birthday.
He made me kill a rabbit.
- A rabbit?
- Yeah.
I guess he thought it would make
me into more of a man or something.
I cried for a week.
Jesus.
What? I'm a fan of Thumper.
[chuckles] I meant your dad.
Yeah.
I guess he and my mother loved
each other at some point, but...
[gun cocks]
I wasn't around for that part.
Um, yeah.
Just, uh, point and shoot.
I don't think my
parents ever loved each other.
They must've married for some reason.
My mom was young.
My dad was older,
but he had a cushy job,
money, came from a good family.
So they bought a nice house
at the end of the cul-de-sac...
and started their nuclear family.
Screw that.
Yeah.
- [beer can clatters]
- [both chuckle]
[dialing]
[line ringing]
- [woman] Hello?
- Hey.
Jim?
- Yeah.
- [sighs]
Why are you calling me
here? I told you not to call me.
I know, I know, I
know. I just wanted to...
I just wanted to hear
your voice and, uh...
I just wanted to say that, um...
even after everything
that happened, I don't...
I don't regret any of it.
And those seven years, they
were... everything to me.
Have you been drinking?
No.
- No.
- [baby crying over phone]
[woman shushing] Honey, hey...
Hey, it's okay... it's okay. [shushing]
[crying continues]
You know what, actually, I
have been drinking, I'm sorry.
Jim, I can't...
Just take care of yourself, okay?
Say hi to Bill for me.
Are you sure...
[phone ringing]
[ringing stops]
[sighs] How much further?
I don't know. These only
tell direction, not distance.
You really need to learn
more about compasses.
I'm just saying.
How do we know when we get to the gate?
Uh, I think a portal to another
dimension is gonna be pretty obvious.
[sighs]
Do you think she's acting weird?
You're asking if the
weirdo is acting weird?
I mean, weirder than normal?
I don't know. Who cares?
[breathing heavily]
How far, Papa?
Farther than we've ever gone before.
- The bath?
- Yes.
Yes, the bath.
Is that okay?
Okay.
Mike.
Yeah?
Turn back.
What? Why?
I'm tired.
[sighs] Look, I'm sure we're almost
there. Just hold on a little longer, okay?
[sighs]
[Nancy] You never
said what I was saying.
[Jonathan] What?
[Nancy] Yesterday.
You said I was saying something and
that's why you took my picture.
Oh, uh...
I don't know.
My guess...
I saw this girl, you
know, trying to be someone else.
But for that moment...
it was like you were
alone, or you thought you were.
And, you know, you
could just be yourself.
That is such bullshit.
[stammers] What?
I am not trying to be someone else.
Just because I'm dating
Steve and you don't like him...
You know what? Forget it. I just
thought it was a good picture.
He's actually a good guy.
[stammers] Okay.
Yesterday, with the camera...
He's not like that at all.
He was just being protective.
Yeah, that's one word for it.
Oh, and I guess what you did was okay?
No, I... I never said that.
He had every right to be pissed...
Okay, all right. Does that
mean I have to like him?
No.
Listen, don't take it
so personally, okay?
I don't like most people.
He's in the vast majority.
You know, I was actually
starting to think that you were okay.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I was thinking, "Jonathan Byers,
maybe he's not the pretentious
creep everyone says he is."
Well, I was just
starting to think you were okay.
- Oh.
- I was thinking, "Nancy Wheeler,
she's not just another suburban
girl who thinks she's rebelling
by doing exactly what every
other suburban girl does...
until that phase passes and they
marry some boring one-time jock
who now works sales,
and they live out a perfectly boring little
life at the end of a cul-de-sac.
Exactly like their parents, who
they thought were so depressing,
but now, hey, they get it."
[scoffs]
[pounding on door]
Go away, Lonnie.
[continues pounding]
Seriously!
I am gonna murd...
[whispers] What? What?
[Hopper sighs]
Oh, Jesus.
[scoffs]
Oh, no.
"Oh, no"? What's, "Oh, no"?
- We're headed back home.
- What?
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Setting sun, right there. We
looped right back around.
And you're just realizing this now?
- Why is this all on me?
- Because you're the compass genius!
What do yours say?
[both] North.
- [Lucas sighs]
- Makes no damn sense.
[sighs] Maybe the gate moved.
No, I don't think it's the gate.
I think it's something else
screwing with the compasses.
Maybe it's something here.
No, it has to be like a super magnet.
It's not a magnet.
She's been acting weirder than normal.
If she can slam doors with her mind,
she can definitely screw up a compass.
Why would she do that?
Because she's trying to
sabotage our mission.
Because she's a traitor!
[Mike] Lucas, what are you doing?
You did it, didn't you?
You don't want us to reach the gate.
You don't want us to find Will.
[Mike] Lucas, come on, seriously,
- just leave her alone!
- Admit it.
- No.
- Admit it!
- Fresh blood. I knew it.
- Lucas, come on!
I saw her wiping her nose on the
tracks! She was using her powers!
Bull! That's old blood. Right, El?
Right, El?
[crying] It's... not...
it's not safe.
- [Hopper panting]
- [light bulbs clattering]
[panting] Okay.
Should be okay, I mean...
I can't guarantee it,
but it should be okay.
What the hell is going on, Hopper?
They bugged my place.
- What?
- They bugged my place.
They put a microphone in the light.
[sighs]
It's because I'm on to
them and they know it.
- I don't know...
- Who?
I thought they might
be watching you, too.
I don't know, the CIA, the NSA, Department
of Energy... I don't know.
You gotta explain this
to me, 'cause I am not...
I went to the morgue last night, Joyce.
What?
It wasn't him.
Will's body, it was a fake.
[Joyce exclaims]
You were right.
This whole time, you were right.
What did I tell you? She's been
playing us from the beginning!
That's not true. She
helped us find Will!
Find Will?
Where is he, then? Huh? I don't see him.
- Yeah, you know what I mean.
- No, I actually don't.
Just think about it, Mike.
She could've just told us
where the Upside Down was right away,
but she didn't.
She just made us run around
like headless chickens.
- All right, calm down!
- No!
She used us, all of us!
She helped just enough so
she could get what she wants.
Food and a bed.
- She's like a stray dog.
- Screw you, Lucas!
No! Screw you, Mike. You're blind...
blind because you like that a
girl's not grossed out by you.
But wake up, man! Wake the hell up!
She knows where Will is,
and now she's just letting
him die in the Upside Down.
- Shut up!
- For all we know, it's her fault.
Shut up.
We're looking for some stupid monster...
but did you ever stop to
think that maybe she's the monster?
I said shut up!
[grunting]
- Stop!
- [Dustin] Knock it off, you idiots.
- Stop it!
- [Dustin] Mike, get off!
- [grunting]
[screams]
Jesus!
Lucas! Lucas! Lucas, are you all right?
- Lucas.
- Lucas, come on!
- Lucas, wake up! Lucas.
- [Dustin] Come on, Lucas!
Why would you do that?
- [Dustin] Come on.
- What's wrong with you?
[distorted] What is wrong with you?
[indistinct overlapping chatter]
[chatter continues]
[man speaking Russian]
[man continues speaking]
[man continues indistinctly on PA]
[speaking Russian]
[growling]
- [distorted snarling on PA]
- What is that?
I have no idea.
[breathing heavily]
[indistinct snarling]
[muffled screaming] Help! Help!
[sobbing]
[Dustin] Come on, wake up. Come on!
Lucas... Lucas, come on!
- [Dustin chuckles]
- [Mike exhales]
[Mike] Lucas.
Lucas, you okay?
[Dustin] Lucas... Lucas, how
many fingers am I holding up?
Lucas, how many fingers?
- [Mike] Let me see your head.
- Get off of me!
[Mike] Just... Lucas. Lucas, let me see.
Get off of me!
- Lucas, come on.
- Let him go.
Man, let him go.
Where is El?
[breathing heavily]
[shouting] El?
- El!
- Eleven!
El!
- El!
Eleven!
[indistinct whimper]
What, are you tired?
Shut up.
What?
I heard something.
[indistinct whimper]
[whimpering continues]
- [Nancy] Oh, God.
- [whimpering]
[Jonathan sighs]
[Nancy] It's been hit by a car.
We can't just leave it.
[whimpering]
I'll do it.
- I thought you said...
- I'm not nine anymore.
[sighs]
- [cocks gun]
- [breathing heavily]
[both gasping]
What was that?
[both panting]
[Nancy] Where'd it go?
I don't know.
Do you see any more blood?
No.
[liquid dripping]
Jonathan?
- [snarling]
- [gasps]
[gnawing]
- [twig snaps]
- [roars]
[screams]
[gasps] Nancy!
Nancy?
Nancy, where are you?
Nancy!
[rock music playing]
-